Guide to the Franklin M. Fisher Papers, 1958-2012 RL.11059
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1958-2010; 1; 10.5 Linear Feet
  - Articles and Essays, 1958-2003; 1
    - On Stability Analysis with Disequilibrium Awareness, 1986-1987 (Box W3)
      Includes two versions
    - On the Analysis of History and the Interdependence of the Social Sciences, 1960 (Box W3)
    - On the Cost of Approximate Specification in Simultaneous Equation Estimation, 1961 (Box W3)
    - On the Goals of the Firm: Comment, 1965 (Box W3)
    - On the Feasibility of Identifying the Crime Function in a Simultaneous Model of Crime Rates and Sanction Levels, 1978 (Box W3)
    - On the Independent Use of Two or More Sets of Policy Variables, 1967 (Box W3)
    - On the Misuse of the Profits-Sales Ratio to Infer Monopoly Power, 1983-1986; 5 folders (Box W3)
      Includes manuscript, report, notes, multiple versions, "The Usefulness of Accounting Profit Data: A Comment on Fisher and McGowan" by William F. Long and David J. Ravenscraft," "The Misuse of Accounting Rates of Return: Reply"
    - On the Relation Between Econometric Sectoral and Macro Models, 1978 (Box W3)
      Includes Working Paper
    - On the Sensitivity of the Level of Output to Savings: Embodiment and Disembodiment: A Clarification Note, 1969 (Box W3)
    - On the Simultaneous Existence of Full and Partial Capital Aggregates, 1983 (Box W3)
    - Optimal Water Management and Conflict Resolution: The Middle East Water Project, 2002 (Box W3)
      Includes Drafts
    - Optimal Water Management in the Middle East and Other Regions, 2001 (Box W3)
    - Organizing Industrial Organization: Reflections on the Handbook of Industrial Organization, 1991 (Box W3)
      Includes research materials, working paper
    - Pan American to United: The Pacific Division Transfer Case, 1986-1987; 3 folders (Box W3)
      Includes multiple versions, drafts, research material
    - The Place of Least Squares in Econometrics: Comment, 1962 (Box W4)
    - Price and Output Aggregation in the Brookings Econometric Model, 1965 (Box W4)
    - Price Index Aggregation: Plutocratic Weights, Democratic Weights and Value Judgments, 2002 (Box W4)
    - The Price of Water and the Value of Economics, undated (Box W4)
      Paper in honor of Hillel Shuval on the occasion of his retirement
    - A Probabalistic Approach to the Evaluation of Losses to Agriculture Due to Water Policies, 2002-2003 (Box W4)
    - Production-Theoretic Input Price Indices and the Measurement of Real Aggregate Input Use, 1985 (Box W4)
      Includes notes, working paper, multiple versions
    - The Production-Theoretic Measurement of Input Price and Quantity Indices, 1994 (Box W4)
    - Properties of the von Neumann Ray in Decomposable and Nearly Decomposable Technologies, 1963 (Box W4)
    - A Proposal for the Distribution Abroad of the United States' Food Surplus, 1962 (Box W4)
    - Quantity Constraints, Spillovers, and the Hahn Process, 1975 (Box W4)
      Includes working paper
    - Quasi-Competitive Price Adjustment by Individual Firms: A Preliminary Paper, 1970 (Box W4)
    - Radical Students and Political Universities, 1970 (Box W4)
    - Reenlistments in the U.S. Navy: A Cost Effectiveness Study, 1967 (Box W4)
    - Reflections on Competition Policy, 1993 (Box W4)
    - Regional Specialization and the Supply of Wheat in the United States, 1867-1914, 1970 (Box W4)
    - The Relative Sensitivity to Specification Error of Different k-class Estimators, 1966 (Box W4)
    - Response of Near-Optimal Agricultural Production to Water Policies, 2000 (Box W4)
    - Restrictions on the Reduced Form and the Rank and Order Conditions, 1966 (Box W4)
    - Returns to Scale in Research and Development: What Does the Schumpeterian Hypothesis Imply?, 1973 (Box W4)
    - The Schumpeterian Hypothesis: Reply, 1979 (Box W4)
    - A Simple Proof of the Fisher-Fuller Theorem, 1972 (Box W4)
    - Simultaneous Equations Estimation: The State of the Art, 1970 (Box W4)
    - The Social Cost of Monopoly and Regulation: Posner Reconsidered, 1984 (Box W4)
    - Stability and Competitive Equilibrium in Two Models of Search and Individual Price Adjustment, 1973 (Box W4)
    - Stability, Disequilibrium Awareness, and the Perception of New Opportunities, 1979; 1981 (Box W4)
    - The Stability of General Equilibrium: Results and Problems, 1975 (Box W4)
    - The Stability of the Cournot Oligopoly Solution: The Effects of Speeds of Adjustment and Increasing Marginal Costs, 1961 (Box W4)
    - Standing Up to be Counted: Issues in the Statistical Adjustment of the Census, 1995 (Box W4)
    - Standing Up to be Counted: The Decision Not to Adjust the 1990 Census, 1992-1995 (Box W4)
      Includes research material
    - "Statistical Indentifiability" in International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1968 (Box W4)
    - Statisticians, Econometricians, and Adversary Proceedings, 1985 (Box W4)
      Includes drafts, notes
    - Sustainability, Efficient Management, and Conflict Resolution in Water, written with Annette Huber-Lee, 2005-2010 (Box A1)
      Includes draft of article, and later presentation pages with similar title
    - Symposium on Marshall's Tendencies: 2. Well-Grounded Theory, and Aggregation, 2002 (Box W4)
    - Syria and Israel: Must Water be a Problem in a Peace Agreement?, undated (Box W4)
    - Taste and Quality Change in the Pure Theory of the True Cost-of-Living Index, undated (Box W4)
    - Technological Change and the Drilling Cost-Depth Relationship: 1960-1966, 1974 (Box W4)
    - Test of Equality Between Sets of Coefficients in Two Linear Regressions: An Expository Note, 1970 (Box W4)
    - A Theoretical Analysis of the Impact of Food Surplus Disposal on Agricultural Production in Recipient Countries, 1963 (Box W4)
    - To Carl Kaysen - in Appreciation, 1992 (Box W4)
    - Towards Cooperation in Water: The Middle-East Water Project, undated (Box W4)
    - Two Theorems on Ceteris Paribus in the Analysis of Dynamic Systems, 1962 (Box W4)
    - Uncorrelated Disturbances and Identifiability Criteria, 1963 (Box W4)
    - U.S. Experience: The Recent INS Study, 1970 (Box W4)
    - U.S. v. Microsoft: An Economic Analysis, 2000 (Box W4)
    - WAS-Guided Cooperation in Water: The Case of the Grand Coalition - reviewer comments, approximately 1999 (Box A1)
    - Water and Peace in the Middle East, 1995 (Box W4)
    - Water: Casus Belli or Source of Cooperation?, 2002 (Box W4)
    - Would Increasing Residential Electric Rates Help Preserve Environmental Quality?, 1971 (Box W4)
    - Zvi Griliches Funeral Address, 1999 (Box W4)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, Reviews, Writings By Others, etc., 1960-2010; 2
    - Assorted Summaries, 1960-1975 (Box W4)
    - Book Reviews, Article Reviews, and Comments on Others' Works, 1960-1999 (Box W5)
    - Miscellaneous Research Material on Input Prices Indices, undated (Box W5)
    - Notes for Disequilibrium Foundation of Equilibrium Economics, undated (Box W5)
    - Notes for Early Stability Paper, 1973 (?) (Box W5)
    - Possible Lerner Example, 1984 (Box W5)
    - Review of John Sutton's Book "Technology and Market Structure: Theory and History"/Proofs of the Book, 2000 (Box W5)
    - Miscellaneous columns and graphics re: aluminum output, wheat, etc., undated (Box W5)
    - New York Times letter to the editor, "Area of Israel", 1967 (Box W5)
    - Kalos, Stephen, and Harry L. Foster: "Viewing 'Janis Joplin's Yearbook' with Hindsight: A New Look at Franklin Fisher's Contributions to the Economics of Damages", approximately 2000 (Box A1)
    - Wu, Xun, and Dale Whittington: "Incentive Compatibility and Conflict Resolution in International River Basins: A Case Study of the Nile Basin", approximately 2008 (Box A1)
    - Rashid, Salim: "Austrian Economics and Economic Verifiability" draft, approximately 2010 (Box A1)
    - Liquid Assets contract, reviewer comments, 2005 (Box A1)
    - Davidson, Michael: Proposal for the Establishment of a Bi-National Water Authority in the Middle East presentation, 2005-2007 (Box A1)
    - Schinkel, Maartin-Pieter: "No Statistical Surprise: Finding a Favorable Surprise for Franklin Fisher", 1999 (Box A1)
  - Books, 1962-1999; 3
    - Contributions to Economic Analysis: A Study in Econometrics: The Demand for Electricity in the United States, 1962 (Box W5)
      Photocopy
    - Supply and Costs in the U.S. Petroleum Industry: Two Econometric Studies, 1964 (Box W5)
    - Formation of Economic Magnitudes: Disequilibrium and Stability, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box W5)
      Drafts, correspondence with editor Jean Cartelier, etc.
    - Disequilibrium Foundations of Equilibrium Economics, 1983-1985 (Box W5)
      Reviews, correspondence
    - Folded, Spindled, and Mutilated: Economic Analysis and U.S. vs. IBM, 1983-1985 (Box W5)
    - Antitrust and Regulation: Essays in Memory of John J. McGowan, 1985 (Box W5)
      Reviews, illustration proofs
    - Developing the But-for World: Estimating Damages in Polaroid vs. Kodak, 1988-1994; 2 folders (Box W5)
      Chapter drafts by Fisher and Robert Dolan; proposal; correspondence
    - Collected Works Vol. 1: Industrial Organization, Economics, and the Law, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box W6)
      Notes, drafts, and correspondence
    - Collected Works Vol. 2: Econometrics, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box W6)
    - Collected Works Vol. 3: Aggregation: Aggregate Production Functions and Related Topics, 1991-1992 (Box W6)
      Notes, drafts, proofs, and correspondence
    - Collected Works Vol. 4: Topics in Theoretical and Applied Economics, 1993-1999; 3 folders (Box W6)
      Drafts, notes, correspondence
  - Work with Karl Shell, 1967-2001; 4
    - Education Loan Project, 1967 (Box W6)
    - The Pure Theory of Output and Input Deflation in an Open Economy, undated (Box W6)
      Notes, drafts, multiple versions
    - The Pure Theory of the National-Output Deflator, 1970 (Box W6)
      Working paper
    - On Perfect Aggregation in the National Output Deflator, undated (Box W6)
    - Correspondence between Shell and Fisher, 1970s-1990s (Box W6)
    - Production Price Indexes book, 1980s; 4 folders (Box W6)
      Seminal Works drafts
    - Production Price Indexes book, 1975-1998; 13 folders (Box W7)
      Includes correspondence between Shell and Fisher; correspondence with editors; research materials; notes; chapter drafts and versions; annexes; reviews; and comments
    - The Theory of Price Indices and Subindices for Output and Input Deflation, 1979-1980; undated; 3 folders (Box W7)
      Proposal, notes, correspondence, multiple versions
    - Outputs Price Indices, 1981 (Box W7)
      Working papers
    - Economic Analysis of Production Price Indexes, 1993-1996 (Box W7)
      Research materials, correspondence
    - Nomination of Shell for the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 2001 (Box W7)
- Consulting Work, 1964-2010; 1
  The majority of Fisher's consulting work relates to his role as a legal expert for a variety of monopoly and anti-trust cases, both as an independent scholar and as a partner in Charles River Associates. Some of the cases represented here had widespread impact on US antitrust law, including US vs. IBM, Eastman Kodak vs. Polaroid, and US vs. Microsoft. The Consulting Work Series also includes materials from Fisher's involvement in assorted projects, in particular Harvard University's Middle East Water Project. Other subseries include Fisher's professional service, his workshops, and his reports. There may be additional materials related to these subseries in the Correspondence, Writings, and Engagements series.
  - Expert Witness Files, 1972-2009; 1
    Fisher's Expert Witness Files include copies of his depositions, court transcripts, supplemental research files, and other materials he acquired in his role as expert witness in a number of legal cases. These materials occasionally include notations that they are confidential; Fisher has attested that they are open for research.
    - American Airlines vs. US Air, 1987 (Box CW1)
      Deposition of F. Fisher
    - American Needle vs. National Football League, 2009 (Box A1)
    - Air Passenger Computer Reservations Systems (CRS) Antitrust Litigation, 1987-1990; 12 folders (Box CW1)
      Includes: US Air vs. American Airlines and United Airlines; Continental Airlines vs. American Airlines and United Airlines; New York Airlines vs. American Airlines and United Airlines; Continental Airlines and Texas International Arilines vs. American Airlines and United Airlines; depositions of Franklin Fisher; identifications of F. Fisher as an expert witness; supplemental identification of F. Fisher as an expert witness; transcripts of proceedings
    - American West Airlines report "Airline Market Power", 1991 (Box CW16)
      With Fisher's annotations
    - "An Analysis of Switched Access Pricing and the Telecommunications Act of 1996" for MCI Telecommunications Corporation (Box CW1)
    - Appendix to reply Comments of the National Association of Broadcasters, 1964 (Box CW1)
      The Fisher Report
    - Arbitration between PGG Industries vs. Pilkington plc: Expert Report of Franklin M. Fisher, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box CW1)
      Includes: Expert Report of F. Fisher, Supplement to Report of Franklin M. Fisher, Rebuttal Expert Report of Franklin M. Fisher, Fisher's Testimony (vol. 1), Deposition of F. Fisher
    - "Architectural Bias in CRS: The Loss of Consumer Welfare." A Special Report by Fanklin M. Fisher, 1992 (Box CW1)
    - Before the Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1964; 1972; 3 folders (Box CW1)
      Appendix to Reply Comments of the National Association of Broadcasters (The Fisher Report), Statement of F. Fisher On Behalf of Various TV Stations, Application of Intermedia, Inc. (KQTV) St. Joseph, Missouri for Construction Permit: Petition to Deny/Statement of F. Fisher
    - Before the Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1983; 3 folders (Box CW2)
      Includes: Comments of CBS Inc. Vol. 1, Comments of CBS Inc. Vol. 2: Appendices, Comments of CBS Inc. on Tentative Decision
    - Benefits and Costs of the Federal Trade Commission's Line of Business Program, 1984 (Box CW2)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield vs. Philip Morris, 2000; 2 folders (Box CW2)
      Includes: Depostions of F. Fisher
    - Brand Name Prescription Drugs Antitrust Litigation, 1995 (Box CW2)
      Expert Report of F. Fisher
    - Bulk Popcorn Antitrust Litigation, 1992 (Box CW2)
    - Calvin Klein vs. Linda Wachner, 2001 (Box CW2)
    - Calvin Klein Trademark Trust and Calvin Klein vs. Linda Wachner et al., 2001 (Box CW2)
      Fisher Exhibits 1 Through 9 to the Deposition of Franklin M. Fisher
    - Carbon Dioxide Antitrust Litigation, 1993; 3 folders (Box CW2)
      Includes: Affidavit of F. Fisher, Deposition of F. Fisher, Class Certification Hearing transcripts
    - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS) vs. American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers, et al., 1973 (Box CW2)
      Transcript of Fisher's Testimony
    - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS) vs. American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers, et al., undated (Box CW3)
    - Chicago Professional Sports Ltd. and WGN Broadcasting Company vs. National Basketball Associtation (NBA), 1993-1994; 17 folders (Box CW3)
      Exhibits 1-13, Depositions of F. Fisher, Affidavit of F. Fisher, Min-U-Scripts/Transcripts of Trial Proceedings
    - Cinerama v. Technicolor, 1989 (Box CW3)
      Report to Council of Cinerama by A. D. Murphy
    - Cisco Systems vs. Alcatel USA, Inc. and Alcatel, S.A., 2004 (Box CW3)
    - City of New York vs. US Department of Commerce, 1989; 1992; 4 folders (Box CW4)
      Depositions of F. Fisher
    - City of New York, et al. vs. US Department of Commerce/City of Atlanta, et al. vs, Mosbacher, et al./Florida House of Representatives vs. Barbara H. Franklin, Secretary of Commerce, 1992 (Box CW4)
      Trial Transcript
    - Leza Coleman, Gayle O'Connor, Dick McMillan, Marie Brasley, Charles Slater and Vicki Korsak, individually, on behalf of the general public and on behalf of all others similarly situated vs. Sacramento Cable Television, a general partnership, and DOES 1 through 10, inclusive, 1993; 2 folders (Box CW4)
    - Continental Airlines vs. American Airlines and AMR Corporation/Northwest Airlines vs. American Airlines and AMR Corporation, 1989; 1993; 6 folders (Box CW4)
      Expert Identification of F. Fisher, Deposition of F. Fisher
    - Cordis Corporation and Telectronics vs. Medtronic, 1988 (Box CW4)
    - Corning Glass vs. Sumitomo, 1989 (Box CW16)
      Correspondence re: Consultant selection
    - Corrugated Container Antitrust Litigation, 1983 (Box CW4)
      Transcript of Proceedings
    - Computer Reservations Systems (CRS) Regulations, 1991; 3 folders (Box CW4)
      Comment on Woodside Travel Management, Affidavit of F. Fisher, Notice of Proposed Ruklemaking/Reply Comments of Northwest Airlines
    - Cynthia Baran, et al. vs. The Register Publishing Company, 1985; 3 folders (Box CW4)
      Deposition of F. Fisher, Continued Deposition of F. Fisher
    - Defendant National Basketball Association's Designation of Franklin M. Fisher as an Expert Witness Pursuant to Rule 26(b)(4), 1993 (Box CW5)
    - Department of Labor vs. Harris Bank, undated (Box CW5)
      Testimony of F. Fisher
    - Domestic Air Transportation Antitrust Litigation, 1984; 1991; 4 folders (Box CW5)
      Affidavits of F. Fisher, Appendices to Defendants' Opposition to Plaintiffs' Amended Consolidated Motion For Class Certification, Direct/Cross/Redirect/Recross Examination of F. Fisher
    - Enforcement Policy Regarding Unfair Exclusionary Conduct in the Air Transportation Industry, 1998 (Box CW5)
      Statement of F. Fisher
    - "Evaluation of the Benefits of the Federal Trade Commision's Line of Business Program" (Bureau of Economics Federal Trade Commissoin), 1984 (Box CW5)
      Includes "The Benefits and Costs of the Federal Trade Commission's Line of Business Program" by F. Fisher
    - "Evaluation of the Validity of American Television and Communications Corporation's Estimate of The Impact of Importing the Signals of WGN-TV and WTCG (TV) or Television Viewing of Local Stations in Columbus, Ohio", 1979 (Box CW5)
    - Greyhound Computer Corporation vs. International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), 1980; 3 folders (Box CW5)
    - Ilhan Bilgutay vs. Uniform Code Council, a Delaware Corporation, NCR Corporation, an Ohio Corporation, and International Business Machines Corporation, a New York Corporation, 1987 (Box CW5)
    - Independent Entertainment Group Inc. vs. National Basketball Association (NBA), et al., 1992 (Box CW5)
      Declaration of F. Fisher
    - The Interface Group, Inc. vs. Gordon Publications, 1983 (Box CW5)
      Affidavit of F. Fisher and Supplementary Affidavit of F. Fisher
    - Intermedia Inc., 1973 (Box CW5)
      Reply Statement of F. Fisher
    - Investigation of Boston Edison, 1998 (Box CW5)
    - International Travel Arrangers (ITA)/NWA [Northwest Airlines] Inc., ca. 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box CW5)
      Exhibits: Miscellaneous
    - International Travel Arrangers (ITA) vs. NWA Inc., Northwest Airlines, Inc., Mainline Travel, Inc., Sun Country Airlines, Inc., and First Bank Security, a Corporation/International Travel Arrangerrs (ITA) vs. NWA, Inc., Northwest Airlines, Inc., Mainline Travel, Inc., and Republic Airlines, Inc., 1985-1991; 12 folders (Box CW6)
      Miscellaneous, Surveys by Mid Continent Research, Oral Deposition of Donald R. House, Ph.D., Depositions of F. Franklin, Exhibits, Trial Transcripts
    - JKC Holding Company LLC vs. Washington Sports Ventures, Inc., 2000; 2 folders (Box CW6)
      Expert Report of F. Fisher, Deposition of F. Fisher
    - King World Productions/Outlet Communications, 1988 (Box CW16)
      Correspondence re: case
    - Lady Grace Stores vs. Corporate Property Investors Real Estate Investment Trust, Limited Access, Inc., Limited Express, Inc., Limited Stores, Inc., Victoria's Secret Stores, Inc., and Victoria's Secret, Inc., 1987 (Box CW7)
      Hearing on Preliminary Injunction
    - Long Lake Energy Corporation vs. Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation, 1991; 2 folders (Box CW7)
      Deposition of F. Franklin, Continued Deposition of F. Franklin
    - Lower Lake Erie Iron Ore Antitrust Litigation, 1989; 2 folders (Box CW7)
      Depositions of F. Franklin
    - Marine Construction Antitrust Litigation, 1984 (Box CW7)
      "Collusion in the Marine Construction Industry: An Economic Analysis" by F. Fisher
    - Major League Baseball Properties vs. Salvino, Inc., 2003 (Box CW7)
    - Marathon Petroleum Company (Formerly Marathon Oil Company)/Phillips Petroleum Company, 1991; 4 folders (Box CW7)
      Appendices of Report of F. Fisher, Expert Report of F. Fisher, Deposition of F. Fisher, Continued Deposition of F. Fisher
    - Mario L. Cuomo, et al. vs. Malcolm Baldrige, Secretary of Commerce, 1984 (Box CW8)
    - McDonnell Douglas Corporation and General Dynamics Corporation vs. The United States, 2001; 2 folders (Box CW8)
    - Mead Data Center vs. West Publishing Company, 1988 (Box CW16)
      Affidavits
    - Exhibits to Memorandum of Points and Authorities in Support of Plaintiff Koplar Communications of California Inc.'s Motion for Partial Summary Judgment, 1984 (Box CW8)
      Affidavit of F. Fisher
    - Mission Resources, Inc.-II vs. Texaco Inc., Texaco Trading and Transportations Inc., Texaco Producing Inc., and Does 1 Through 99, Inclusive, 1994 (Box CW8)
    - National Football League vs. Los Angeles Raiders/Oakland Raiders vs. National Football League and The Five Smiths, Inc., et al., 1997 (Box CW8)
      Expert Reports of F. Fisher
    - Outlet Communications, Inc. vs. King World Productions, Inc., 1988 (Box CW8)
    - Pacific Division Transfer Case: Joint Application of Pan American World Airways, Inc. and United Airlines, Inc., 1985; 3 folders (Box CW8)
      Exhibits, Post-Hearing Brief on the United States Department of Justice, Testimony by F. Fisher, Other Testimonies
    - "Petroleum: Facts and Figures," American Petroleum Institute, 1959 (Box CW8)
    - Petroleum Products Antitrust Litigation, 1991-1992; 6 folders (Box CW8)
      Depositions of F. Fisher, Coordinated Pretrial Proceedings
    - Polaroid Corporation vs. Eastman Kodak Company, 1989; 4 folders (Box CW9)
      Trial Transcripts
    - Polaroid Corporation vs. Eastman Kodak Company, undated; 2 folders (Box CW16)
      Untitled book and slides prepared by Fisher for Polaroid case
    - Pulse One Communications, Inc., et al. vs. Bell Atlantic Mobile Systems, 1991; 2 folders (Box CW9)
      Deposition of F. Fisher, Affidavit of F. Fisher
    - Ralph C. Wilson Industries, Inc. vs. Chronicle Broadcasting Company, et al., 1983 (Box CW9)
    - Rebuttal/Defense Expert Report of Roger G. Noll ("Noll Rebuttal"), 1998 (Box CW9)
    - Sanford Manor Associates: Summary of Terms of the Offering, undated (Box CW9)
    - Southeast Florida Cable, Inc., a Florida corporation, d/b/a Adelphia Cable Communications vs. Martin County, a political subdivision of the State of Florida, Marshal L. Wilcox, Donna Sutter Melzer, Janet K. Getting, Dennis Armstrong, and Elmira R. Gainey, as they are members of the Martin County Board of County Commissioners and not individually, and Comcast Cablevision of West Palm Beach, Inc., a Florida Corporation, 1998 (Box CW9)
    - Star Markets, Ltd., a Hawaii Corporation vs. Texaco, Inc., a Delaware Corporation, 1996 (Box CW9)
    - State of New York, County of New York/United States vs. National Broadcasting Company (NBC), 1977 (Box CW9)
    - St. Louis Convention and Visitors Commission vs. National Football League (NFL), et al., 1997; 7 folders (Box CW9)